[
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 18, 4, 4, 18, 4, 19, 4, 19?",
    "correctAnswer": "4",
    "options": [
      "4",
      "5",
      "6",
      "18"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 19, 12, 18, 19, 18, 19, 19, 12?",
    "correctAnswer": "19",
    "options": [
      "19",
      "20",
      "21"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 12, 12, 10, 10, 12, 12, 2, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "12",
    "options": [
      "12",
      "13",
      "14"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 17, 2, 2, 2, 12, 12, 17, 2?",
    "correctAnswer": "2",
    "options": [
      "2",
      "3",
      "4",
      "12"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 11, 16, 18, 18, 18, 11, 16, 18?",
    "correctAnswer": "18",
    "options": [
      "11",
      "18",
      "19",
      "20"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 9, 3, 9, 2, 2, 9, 9?",
    "correctAnswer": "9",
    "options": [
      "9",
      "10",
      "11"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 3, 3, 13, 3, 1, 1, 13, 3?",
    "correctAnswer": "3",
    "options": [
      "3",
      "4",
      "5",
      "13"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 8, 8, 2, 8, 2, 8, 6, 6?",
    "correctAnswer": "8",
    "options": [
      "6",
      "8",
      "9",
      "10"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 9, 15, 5, 9, 5, 5, 5, 15?",
    "correctAnswer": "5",
    "options": [
      "5",
      "6",
      "7",
      "15"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the mode <br> of 17, 7, 10, 10, 17, 7, 7, 7?",
    "correctAnswer": "7",
    "options": [
      "7",
      "8",
      "9",
      "17"
    ]
  }
]